《铁血战士2》
热浪还在继续 洛杉矶已高达109华氏度
The heat wave continues. it's 109 degrees in los angeles.
洛杉矶饱受干旱之苦
As drought-ridden los angeles
高温使人们备受折磨
swelters in agonising heat,...
而街头的毒品稽查也在如火如荼的进行
..drug lords wage warfare in the streets.
又一次公开对抗还在...
Yet another open conflict...
天哪 快带我离开这
oh, fuck this! get me out of here!
有两名骑警在火拼中受重伤
Two motorcycle officers horribly wounded in a crossfire,...
警方似乎无力解救他们
The police seemingly unable to rescue them
多次英勇的突围都没有成功
in spite of several desperate,heroic attempts.
这里已经完全失去控制
It's completely out of control down here.
我辛苦经营的酒吧全没了
My beautiful cantina, everything I own,
什么都被打碎了
they shot it to pieces.
我的微波炉 自动蒸锅 烤箱
My microwave, my automatic steamer, my grill...
你们这群混蛋
You fucking pendejos!
去你们他妈的
Fuck you!
我是托尼·普波 这里是核心现场节目
Tony pope, live with hard core
为您做现场报道
on the scene andin yourface.
这里就像但丁描写的地狱
It's like dante's hell.
硝烟 枪声和难以忍受的高温...
Smoke, fire, oppressive heat,...
哥伦比亚和牙买加的大烟鬼
As colombian and jamaican drug fiends
再次把洛杉矶变成了屠宰场
Again transform LA into a slaughterhouse.
这里到底谁说了算 警察吗 非也
Who the hell's in charge down here? the cops?Uh-uh
他们是人数众多 装备精良的笨蛋
They're outmanned, outgunned and incompetent.
在塔霍湖家中度假的市长先生
Mr mayor, on vacation in your home in lake tahoe,...
快把烟头放下 赶快到这来颁布戒严令
..get off your butt, get down here and declare martial law!
别让我心神不宁 丹尼
Ok, don't keep me in suspense, danny boy!
今天真不太平
It has not been a nice day!
两辆摩托倒在卡车那儿
Two motors pulled over a truck,
刚好挡住了中间缉毒警的视线
Stumbled right in the middle of a narc stakeout.
十个全副武装的哥伦比亚人就足以对付我们
You know, ten colombians and scorpios armed to fuck all.
他们想回老巢
They're trying to get in their headquarters.
我们得阻止他们
We're keeping them pinned down.
不过那些警察就快因出血过多而死了
but those officers are bleeding to death.
他们快不行了 警官
Fuck! they're dying, man.
他妈的重武器在哪儿
Where the hell is special weapons?
它们还在圣佩德罗和牙买加人交火
They're still tied up in that shootout in san pedro with the jamaicans.
他们击落了一架直升机
They shot down a chopper.
米尔斯和詹森快顶不住了
Mills and Johnson won't last much longer.
我们需要一辆装甲车去救他们
We need an assault vehicle to go get 'em.
好吧 我来想想办法
I'm gonna chat with these assholes.
- 看我信号 给我火力掩护 - 明白
- When I give the signal, give me some cover! - Got it!
这也太小了
Too small.
就这样吧
Right.
快点 快点
Come on! come on!
快带他们离开这儿
Get 'em out of here! now!
来吧
Vamonos!
动作快点
Get 'em out! get 'em out!
- 来吧 - 来吧
- Vamonos! - Vamonos!
你们这些狗杂种
Hey, assholes!
迈克 你没事吧
Mike, are you ok?
没事 快去抓那些余孽
yeah. let's get the rest.
不行 海纳曼指挥官有命令
we can't. orders from chief heinemann.
让我们原地待命
He says surround building and wait.
- 待什么命 - 我怎么知道
- Wait for what? - I don't know!
也许是特种部队 联邦探员 毒品管制局
Some bullshit special unit. the feds, the dea.
如果等那帮家伙来插手
If we let those bastards get dug in now
我们得将这座房子夷为平地才能抓住他们
we'll have to level the building to get them out
- 狗娘养的 - 没错
- Hijo de puta. - No, es para mi.
来吧 行动吧
Vamonos!vamonos!
赶快来吧
Venga!aprisa!
来吧
Venga!
我们准备好了 来吧
Come and get it. ei scorpio is ready.
- 警官 上面有你们的人吗 - 没有
- Sarge, any of your people in the building? - No.
行动
Let's go.
中尉 你不能进去 海纳曼马上就到
Lieutenant, can't let you in. Heinemann's on his way.
让他去死吧 动作快点
Heinemann can kiss my sweet ass! come on!
该死的 跟上他
Goddamn it. go with him.
三 二 一
Three, two, one...
行动
Go!
出去 退后
Get back, back, back. back.
隔壁也检查完毕
Next door over.
在门口守着
Take this room!
我们在二楼 有人受伤 请求支援
First floor, officer down. we need backup.
别动
Freeze!
我说别动
I said hold it!
把枪放下
Now, lay your guns down.
是走下来还是跳下去随你便
you can walk down or fly, it's your choice.
但先把枪放下 混蛋
I said put it down, asshole!
不
No!
过去看看
let's do it now!
放松
Take it easy.
真他妈热
Damn, it's hot.
肯定是眼花了
Must be losing it.
迈克
Mike!
散开 搜查整个屋顶
Spread out. secure the roof.
没事了 我在这
Just take it easy. I'm righthere.
警报解除 一切正常
All clear. all clear on the site.
丹尼
Oh, dannyboy.
我得下去了
I gotta get down from here.
天哪
Shit.
全面搜查 哪层都不要放过
Ok, search the roof. check every floor.
也许还有余党
maybe someone else...
把这里封锁起来 不许任何人离开
Seal it off. no one leaves.
丹尼 快让我离开这鬼地方
Danny, get me off this damn roof.
- 找到他们的同党了吗 - 有人捷足先登了
- You get the rest of them? - Somebody beat us to it.
利昂娜
Leona.
我的天哪
Oh, shit.
这儿发生了什么
what happened to ei scorpio?
他正在吃午餐
He's out front having lunch.
这究竟是怎么回事
What the hell is this?
我不知道
I don't know.
他们都身首异处
They've been cut to pieces.
肯定是牙买加人
must be the jamaicans.
像他们的风格 但他们去哪儿了呢
their style, but where the hell did they go?
法医来以前 不准任何人进这里
Ok, nobody gets in here until forensic arrives. nobody.
你知道程序的
Ok, you know the drill.
迈克 你看上面
Mike. Up there.
他肯定是在这儿被杀 然后有人...
He must have been killed out here, and then someone...
起码有35到40英尺高 没有绳子和梯子
That's about 35, 40 feet. no rope, no ladder.
这家伙有190到195磅
The guy weighs about 190, 195 pounds.
你肯定不能把他挂在那
You couldn't carry him up there.
中尉
Lieutenant?
副指挥官海纳曼在楼下
Deputy chief heinemann's downstairs.
他要你和你的人赶快离开这儿
he wants you and your people out of the building now.
这个混蛋
Ah, son of a bitch.
到底发生了什么事
What the fuck is going on?
这不是好兆头 迈克 一点都不好
This is not good, mike. not good at all.
- 查查这家伙的底细 - 我会的
- I want a real name on this joker, ok?  - You got it.
迈克
Mike.
菲尔 你怎么也在这儿
Phil, this is quite a surprise.
什么风把你吹来了
what brings you down from the palace?
迈克 你让我很失望 我现在很不高兴
You let me down, mike. you're making me look bad.
我以为我们已经达成共识
I thought we had an understanding.
我费尽心思让你到这来
I put my ass on the line to get you here,...
只希望你能合作一点
..and all I expect is a little cooperation!
我告诉过你这是联邦调查局的案子
You were told this was a federal matter.
你最好别插手 你竟然违抗命令
Yet you disobeyed an order to stay out of the building.
别这样说 菲尔 是战争带我来的
Don't let this get out, phil, but it's a fucking war down here.
当兵就要服从命令 别找借口
Soldiers take orders. don't push it!
菲尔 我没有找借口
I'll push it as far as I can, phil
当你们在市区办公室里转铅笔的时候
cos we're fighting for our lives here,...
我们在这儿冒死战斗
..while you're downtown pushing pencils and kissing ass!
我不会听任何人的 特别是联邦调查局
I don't roll over for anybody, especially the feds,...
除非给我们一个好的解释
..without a goddamn good explanation!
把这些仪器搬去三楼
Take this equipment up to the third floor.
开始行动
come on, let's move!
- 走吧 - 对不起 长官
- Let's go. - Excuse me, sir!
海纳曼 他们到底在干什么
What the hell is going on here, heinemann?
不听指挥
Insubordination.
不服从上级领导的命令
disregard for direct orders from a supervising officer.
滚回你阿瓦拉多的窝吧
Now get back to your cage at alvarado.
我让你见识见识什么是不听指挥 你个...
I'll show you insubordination, you son of...
别
No, no, no!
你跑什么 有种过来
Where you running to? come here!
没必要这样 迈克 何必呢
You don't need this, mike. it's not worth it.
放松一点
Relax.
真他妈的
Oh, fuck!
我为您带来最新报道
I have an update for you.
这次交火 五名哥伦比亚毒贩
In a shootout, five members of one colombian drug gang...
被他们的对手杀害
..were ambushed by their bloody rivals,
牙买加的伏都教徒神秘失踪
the jamaican voodoo posse, who escaped withouta trace
再次愚弄了...
again making total fools of...
- 有位警官想见你 - 在那后面
- A detective is here to see you. - Back there.
听着 女士 你家厕所漏水
Listen, lady, you got a backed-up toilet.
需要的是水管工而不是警察
Call a plumber, not the cops.
你的执照过期了
This licence has expired.
胡扯 我六个月前付过钱了
Bullshit! I paid that fee six months ago.
- 小心我揍你 - 坐下 赶快
- I'll kick your ass! - Sit down! right now!
- 走 快走 - 你他妈冷静点
- Move! get your ass movin'! - Just calm the fuck down!
你在看什么
What you lookin' at?
你要做的就是
And all you got to do...
把球放在球座上 然后挥杆
..is tee it high and let it fly.
完美的挥杆
Ow! dead solid perfect.
你要记住
Now, remember
你要看好距离 紧紧地抓住球杆
for distance you gotta gently but firmly grip the club.
哈里根中尉 我是探员兰伯特 防卫司的
Lieutenant harrigan! detective lambert, rampart division.
小伙子 先坐一会 我一会找你
Hey, kid, just have a seat. I'll be right with you.
- 嘿 头 - 你先别说 迈克
- Hey, cap. - Don't start, mike.
海纳曼已经警告我
Heinemann's already been up my ass so
让我小心我头上的乌纱帽
Far I won't be able to sit down for a week.
我们赢不了他
We're not winning this war.
不管你愿不愿意 有些事你必须要做
As much as it'll piss you off, you'll have to play the game.
而且必须立即去做
"effective immediately,
联邦特遣队负责人彼得·凯斯
A federal task force under special agent peter keyes...
会调查一系列犯罪活动
Will investigate criminal activities
包括一些受限案件
Involving the trafficking of controlled substances."
你要全力配合他
And you will extend him your full cooperation.
你是要我把案子交给他吗
So you're cutting off my dick and shoving it up my ass.
联邦调查局是老大 我们得听它的
The feds are calling the shots on this. my hands are tied!
什么事
Peah?
皮尔格瑞姆上尉 我是彼得·凯斯
Captain pilgrim, peter keyes.
- 很高兴见到你 - 我也是 长官
- It's good to meet you. - And you, sir.
迈克·哈里根中尉 联邦调查局探员彼得·凯斯
Lieutenant mike harrigan. special agent peter keyes, dea.
久仰大名
Heard a lot about you.
很抱歉 这是司法程序
I'm sorry for this jurisdictional intrusion.
不是说我比你们权力大
Don't mean to be stepping on your toes.
我们只是想铲除金·威利的伏都教
But we want to prevent king willie's voodoo
他们控制了整个西海岸
Gangs from taking over the entire west coast.
我想多透露一些给你们
I wish I could tell you more.
但这牵涉到一些核心问题
But we have a large number of deep-cover operatives involved.
你们知道的 我们都有各自的职责
You know how it is. we all have a job to do.
现在 我保证
Now, I'm sure
我们会尊重彼此并各司其职
we can respect each other's situation and act responsibly.
合作是我突出的个性
Well,...um, cooperation...is my middle name.
一会见
I'll see you around.
我刚调过来 我叫吉瑞·兰伯特
I'm the new transfer, jerry lambert.
听我说 你先坐一会
Like I said, have a seat.
一会找你
I'll be right with you.
- 这个公子哥是谁 - 一个笨蛋
- Who is this dude? - Yeah, what an asshole.
丹尼 查到什么了
All right, danny boy, what we got?
查到什么?
What have we got?
里面是五个来历不明人
five lowlife scorpions make it into the building.
然后 他们变成了烤肉串
The next minute... they're all shish kebab.
没有枪伤
Not one bullet wound.
不是为了毒品和钱 因为这些东西撒了一地
It wasn't drugs or money. there's a shit load of that.
也许金·威利雇了某个厉害角色
Maybe king willie brought in some outside talent.
他正显示他的本事
He's making his big move.
他在我们上去之前已经解决了战斗
A pro would have split the moment he heard us.
不止杀了一个人 也许我们见到他了
More than one, we would have seen them.
究竟是谁在最后时刻
Whoever did this waited until the last minute,...
将四个手持机枪的
..and then took out four men
悍匪统统放倒
armed with machine guns by hand!
然后在我们眼皮底下溜走了呢
And then got by us.
也许我们应该雇佣他
let's put him on the payroll.Maybe we should give him a job.
当我和我搭档守在楼梯上时
So me and my partner bolt up the stairs,
有人大叫血腥谋杀
Somebody is screaming bloody murder...
- 你听我说 - 什么
- You gotta... you gotta hear this. - What?!
嘿 忘了告诉你
Hey. hey, I forgot to tell you.
看见那家伙了吗
See that guy there?
他会接菲利斯的班
That's ferris's replacement.
他叫吉瑞·兰伯特
This guy's jerry lambert.
是防卫司的独行侠
the lone ranger from rampart station.
有他那样的独行侠吗
That's the lone ranger?
我还以为他是来这儿修空调的
I thought he was here to fix the air conditioning.
我就说"女士你被捕了" 她说"为什么"
I said "lady, you are under arrest." and she said "why?"
我说"因为你杀死了你丈夫"
I said "because your husband is dead. you killed him."
- 你知道她说什么 - 不知道
- You know what she said, didn't miss a beat? - uh, no.
她说"我以前常常这么刺这个混蛋
She said "i stabbed that son of a bitch plenty of times.
可他都没死啊"
He never died on me before."
他好像在挑逗利昂娜
Looks like he's putting the moves to leona.
他犯的第一个大错误
His first big mistake.
我听说过你
I have heard about you.
- 真的吗 - 没错
- Yeah? - Yeah!
- 比如你上个搭档被枪击 - 什么
- Like your last partner got shot. - What?
别老缠着我 笨蛋
You try that cowboy shit with me, fucker,...
要不然我把你阉了
..you can kiss these goodbye.
- 明白了吗 - 明白了
- Got it? - Yeah, I got it. unhh!
我想你已经见过三位了
Well, well, I see that the three of you have met.
兰伯特 如果你还忍得住
Lambert, if you're feeling up to it,...
可以慢慢地走到中尉那
..why don't you limp your way in to the lieutenant.
他想和你谈谈
He wants to talk to you.
好的
Yeah.
- 你真是个坏女孩 - 我喜欢这样
- You're a bad girl. - Ooh, I like that.
不 不 不
No, no, no!
天哪 这女人是不是来月经了
Goddamn, is that bitch on the rag or what?
小伙子 接下来我所说的就是所谓的"规矩"
This is what I call "the speech", kid.
我只说一次 注意听
I only give it once, so pay attention.
到目前为止 都是些小打小闹的游戏
Until now, it's all been fun and games, cops and robbers,
还有油炸圈
Dunking doughnuts.
但现在不一样了 我得告诉你这是个战区
But you're in the shit now. metro command is a war zone.
中尉 我明白
Lieutenant, I've paid my dues.
我费了很多功夫才调到这
I had to bust my ass to get my transfer.
这让我很吃惊 小伙子
And that scares the shit out of me, kid.
没人会要求到这来
No one requests to come here
除非他想扬名立万
unless they want a reputation.
这里没有地方让人表现自己
There's no room for anyone looking to prove themselves.
我也绝不允许这样
I won't stand for it.
别让我不高兴
Don't get me wrong.
我们需要好警察
We need good cops
他们说你很棒
and they say you're good at what you do.
但是团队精神是第一位的
But the team comes first.
以团队为主 才是重要的
You live by that, and you'll be ok.
我们在等着你
and we'll all be there for you.
记住 凡事都有两面
Remember, the door swings both ways.
就这些
That's it.
嘿 小伙子
Hey, kid.
欢迎加入战斗
Welcome to the war.
小子 是不是做的太过火了
Ok, guys. this has gone too far now, huh?
听着 小子
Hey, hey, guys.
我知道你想恐吓我
I-l-l know you're trying to scare me, huh?
你做的很好
Well, you did a pretty good job, man.
我现在很害怕
I'm scared now.
别这样
Stop it now.
我给你钱
I can pay you.
两百万现钞 马上就给
$2 million, man. in cash. right now!
不是钱的问题
This is not about money.
是权利之争
This is about power!
这里会有新老大
There's a new king in the streets.
这是给你和你的手下提个醒
This is a message he has for your people.
你的时代过去了
You are history.
该死的历史 普托
Fucking history, goddamn puto.
你他妈在干什么
What the fuck are you doing now, man?
你疯了吗
You're crazy!
金·威利说
King willie says...
我不仅能杀死你的肉体
..not only do I have to kill you,...
还能带走你的灵魂
..but I have to take your soul.
伏都教的咒语
Voodoo magic.
该死的伏都教
Fucking voodoo magic, man.
但你知道吗 我来告诉你我的信仰
But you know what? I tell you what I believe.
好戏上演
Shit happens.
快开枪
Shoot it!
混蛋
Fucker!
好戏上演
Sh... shit happens.
Shit happens.
我现在在圣佩德罗的别墅区外
I'm standing just outside a penthouse complex in san pedro...
有20人死亡
..involving as many as 20 people.
死者身份不明
it's uncertain who they were.
有报告指出
One report indicates
也许是恐怖的牙买加伏都教徒
It might be the feared jamaican voodoo posse.
我去做身体检查 我的医生说
I go in for my physical and the doctor says
"我需要精子 大便和尿样"
"i need a semen,Stool and urine sample."
我说"医生 我很忙
I say "gee, doc, I'm in a big hurry.
我能不能只把内裤留下"
can I just leave my underwear?"
上帝啊
Oh, god.
有消息称
Word is
里面至少有50具尸体
there may be as many as 50 more dead bodies up there.
看那 是波普
Oh, man, it's pope.
那个寄生虫肯定住在车上
That parasite must live in his car.
我来处理 公共关系我最拿手了
I'll handle it. pr's my specialty.
他们说让你别沾手这个案子
Word is they want your ass off the job.
- 托尼 伙计 - 你是谁
- tony, my man! - who the hell are you?
我是你最忠实的粉丝 每次都看你的演出
Your biggest fan! catch your show all the time.
- 我还有工作要做 - 你要做的就是滚远点
- I got a job to do! - Your job is to root garbage for elsewhere.
进去过了?
Been inside?
是的 我们几个当时正要进去
Yeah. we were gonna go in with our guys,...
但是接到无线电通知说
But we were told on a radio
不管发生什么 任何人都不能进去
Transmission nobody goes in under any circumstances.
所有单位注意
All units, be advised.
联邦调查员将接手调查
federal offcers will handle investigation.
- 我们什么都没听到 走 - 你是老大
- we didn't hear that. let's go. - you're the boss.
谢丽尔·泰尔在现场为您报道...
This is cheryl tyer reporting live...
这手电筒真不错 介意我借用一下吗
Hey, nice flashlight. mind if I borrow it?
该死
Damn!
很眼熟
Look familiar?
操
Fuck.
老天
Oh, god.
雷蒙·维嘉 那个大毒枭
Ramon vega, the crack king.
是东洛杉矶最大的贩子 每周卖出100公斤
Biggest operator in east LA. 100 kils a week.
为什么他没被剥皮 这些混蛋是什么人
Why isn't he skinned? and who are they assholes?
是牙买加人
they are jamaicans.
金·威利的手下
King willie's boys.
这毫无意义
That makes no sense.
是伏都教仪式 我见过 他们挖出他的心
This was a voodoo ritual. I've seen it before. they took his heart out.
- 为了什么 - 都是吓人的方法
- what for? - Terror tactics, man.
为了把敌人吓得屁滚尿流
You know, to scare the shit out of their enemies.
- 金·威利 - 谁是该死的金·威利
- king willie. - who the hell is king willie?
金·威利 伏都教洛杉矶分教的神父
King willie, voodoo priest of the LA posses.
在他的势力变得强大前
Ran the terror gangs for Edward seaga in Jamaica...
帮爱德华·西嘉在牙买加运营恐怖组织
..till he got too powerful.
没他允许 牙买加的头头们都不敢有所行动
The Jamaican chiefs won't make a move without his approval.
他妈的到底发生了什么
So what the fuck happened?
该死!
Shit!
这里有个幸存者
Hey, we got a survivor!
她在说什么
What's she saying?
不知道 听不清她在说什么
I don't know. she's not making any sense.
她一直在说"恶魔来找他们了"
She keeps saying "ei diablo vino por ellos." the devil came for them.
如果这是那些哥伦比亚人干的
If it's the colombians did this,
为什么他们不管吊着的老大和裸体的女友
Why'd they leave their boss hanging and his girl naked on the floor?
这不是哥伦比亚人干的
It wasn't the colombians.
难道是军火库的人?
Our friend from the armoury?
是的
Right.
我们有新的对手了
We got a new player in town.
过来 迈克 看看这个
Come over here, mike. check this out.
那是什么
What is that?
看起来像矛头或是什么的
Looks like a spear tip or something.
这里是禁区
This is a restricted area.
我希望你们马上消失
I want it cleared immediately.
你正站在证据上面
You're walking on physical evidence.
- 我们来照顾她 - 我来 你们退后
- We'll take care of her. - She's with me.Just back off!
中尉 我想单独跟你谈谈
Lieutenant, I'd like a word with you in private, please.
他们说坚持不懈是你最大的优点
They say that persistence is what your most outstanding quality.
- 我知道这事归你管... - 你没听我说话
- I know this is your show... - you're not listening to me!
你太多管闲事 而且你干涉了太多我的工作
You got a big nose and you're sticking it too far in my business.
你听好了 下次如果你再越界
Maybe you can hear this. the next time you cross me,...
你会永远消失
you're gonna turn up missing.
盖博 快把那个摄影师赶出去
Garber, the man with the camera.Get him.Right now!
是 长官
Yes, sir.
- 快点走开 - 站边上点
- All right. Come on.let's go. - Stay away.
- 我操 把我的摄像机还给我 - 给我闭嘴
- Hey, fuck you, man! give me my camera! - Shut the fuck up.
等等 我有权在这儿 我是一名记者
Hey, wait a minute! I got my rights! I'm a journalist.
- 哈里根 - 闭嘴 快走
- harrigan! harrigan! - shut up. let's go.
你们想掩饰些什么 媒体有权知道
Smells like a cover-up. the press has a right to know!
把他带出大楼 搜他的身
Take him out of the building. search him.
你也给我滚出去
Now you get the hell out of here.
你是哪根葱 凯斯
Who the hell are you, keyes?
是这个世界上你唯一不想惹的人
The last person in the world you wanna fuck with.
想让我为你骄傲吗 孩子
Wanna make me proud, kid?
尽你所能 跟住他们 查出他们带她去哪儿
Take your bag of tricks, stay with them, find out where they take her.
稍后在洛杉矶赛塔酒吧见
Meet me later at la cita's.
小心 这些家伙不好惹
And be careful. these guys are good.
不用担心 监视是我的特长
Hey, don't worry! surveillance is my specialty.
很好 开始行动吧
Ok, then. just get going.
找到他们 独行侠
Go get 'em, lone ranger.
丹尼 听着 我们要好好处理这件事
Danny, look here. we gotta take this real cool.
这些家伙虽然不是毒品管制局的人
These guys sure aren't the dea
但仍是凯斯的手下
But it's still keyes's party.
你呆在这儿 不要被发现了 我一点来见你
You stick around, stay out of sight. I'll meet you at one o'clock.
我们再好好搜查一下那房间 如何? 等我
We'll take a good look at that room, ok? hey, wait for me.
丹尼 不要逞英雄 明白吗?
Danny boy, no hero stuff, understand?
丹丹 小丹尼
Dan-dan-dannyboy.
小心点 丹尼
Watch your ass, danny boy.
她没有去医院
She never made it.
联邦调查员就在那等着
The feds were waiting.
直接把她载上了直升飞机
Hustled her off in a chopper.
我猜猜 那架银色云雀式直升机?
Let me guess. a silver alouette?
就是那架
That very one.
知道吗 你的老朋友凯斯
And guess what. your pal keyes was running the whole show.
跟他的愚蠢的跟班 操纵着整个过程
And his butt boys.
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
你做得非常出色 小伙子
You done real good, kid.
明天 开始跟踪凯斯
Now tomorrow, start a tail on keyes.
注意他的一举一动
Everything he does, every where he goes.
你会交上好运的
Who knows? you might just get lucky.
中尉
Lieutenant!
交好运
Luck...
...是我的特长
...is my specialty.
我深信不疑
Yeah. I bet it is.
不好意思 失陪一下 中尉
Now, if you'll excuse me, lieutenant,
我有一些重要的工作要做
I got some serious police work to attend to.
小妞我来了
Come to papa.
- 你的蛋蛋还好吧了? - 很好
- Hey, are your balls ok? - Fine.
你的呢
How are yours?
- 不好意思 她是我妹妹 - 什么
- Hey, do you mind? it's my sister. - Say what?
其实你不是
Oh, you're not my sister,aren't you.
混蛋 你到底在找谁 凯斯
Son of a bitch. who are you really chasing, keyes?
该开工了
Time to go to work.
- 该死的 - 丹尼
- Shit.  - Dannyboy.
迈克
Mike?
老天
Oh, god!
不 不 上帝啊!
No. no. oh, god!
圣母玛利亚
oh, mother of god!
求你别杀我
please, no!
...有暴力倾向 为强迫型人格
...violence prone, obsessive/compulsive personality,
惯用武力
...a history of excessive physical force...
...做了18年的洛杉矶警察
...throughout his 18 years as a los angeles police offcer.
对11辆警车和1辆公共汽车的损坏
Also responsible for the destruction
有着不可推卸的责任
of 11 patrol cars, a citybus...
那你又怎么看他在警局期间
What about ten commendations for valour...
多达10次的嘉奖
What about ten commendations for valour
以及屡破重案的记录
and the best felony arrest record in the history of this department?
因为我的干预
That and my intervention on your behalf
你才能保住你的乌纱帽
Are the only reasons you still have a job.
但是如果让局长知道的话
If it were up to the chief,
他会就丹尼的死起诉你并停你的职
He'd charge you with detective archuleta's death and suspend you.
事实上 他把这件事交给了我处理
As it is, he left it in my hands.
现在 这种无视政策
Now,This John wayne attitude
一意孤行作风将不复存在
flagrant disregard for policy is gonna end now.
在我的指挥下
No one under my command will
没有人能阻止这次由凯斯领导的
impede the progress of this federal task force
联邦调查行动
headed by agent Keyes.
没有人
No one.
就这样
That's it.
散会
Dismissed.
迈克 你管得太多了 放手吧
Mike, you're too close to this. stay out of it.
这是警察的事 他们不能让警察局撒手不管
It's a police matter. they can't keep the department out of it.
我们会找到杀害丹尼的人的
We'll find Danny's killer.
队长 我和丹尼一起在街头
Captain, Danny and I came up together.
巡逻了15年
15 years on the fucking street!
不管谁杀了丹尼 我都会让他血债血偿
Whoever killed him's gonna pay. I'm gonna finish it.
挤什么呀
Hey, come on. what is this?
听好了 混蛋
Listen, shithead.
我不管你要对那个混蛋怎么样
I don't give a fuck what you want with
因为现在这是我的私事
this asshole because now it's personal.
他死定了
And he's a dead man.
你现在的行为超出了你的权限 我警告你
What you're dealing with is over your head. I'm warning you...
你根本不知道你在干什么
You! you don't know what you're dealing with.
该是我警告你 别他妈挡着我的路
And I'm warning you. stay the fuck out of my way!
- 我来收拾他 - 不
- I'll take care of him. - No.
由他去
Let him go.
我们快得手了
We're too close.
诚如所说
Claiming as his
牙买加和哥伦比亚毒枭掌握着真相
turf controlled by the jamaican and colombian drug lords.
请继续看我们接下来的报道
Watch as we continue our report.
洛杉矶已经唾手可得
LA is up for grabs,
这座曾经美好的城市将落入那些
the spoils of our once fine city going to the ruthless scum...
肆意制造屠杀和流血事件的人渣手中
who can spread the most carnage and blood in our streets.
五个混蛋人渣和一名优秀的警察
Five assorted trash and one good cop
警局中最优秀的一员
one of the best on our force.
谁将是下一个受害者 而市长又在哪儿
Who's next? where's the mayor?
他甚至根本就不在洛杉矶...
He's not even in the city...
忘了他吧 都结束了
Forget it. it's over.
迈克 该死
Mike, god damn it.
知道吗 这不是你一个人的战斗
This ain't your personal little war, you know.
我也爱丹尼
I loved Danny, too.
你告诉我们只有团队作战才能存活
Hey, you told me the only way you survive is because you're a team.
凡事都有两面 记得吗
The door swings both ways. remember?
好吧 我们并肩作战
All right. we'll do it together.
告诉我一些关于凯斯的情况
Come on. talk to me about keyes.
过去三天我们一直在跟踪他
we've been on him for the last three days.
他们根本就没有找毒贩子
and they're not looking for drug dealers.
而是在全市区安装那些奇怪的雷达探测器
Yeah. they've been setting up weird radar sensors all over downtown.
我用尽了一切办法去跟着他们
I used my whole repertory to keep up with them!
我尝试用探测器扫描他们 但是被他们察觉了
I had scanners on them, but they scrambled my shit up.
他们的设备太先进 我根本无法靠近
They had equipment I can't begin to touch.
今天早晨...
And then this morning...
- 我把他们跟丢了 - 我们把他们跟丢了
- l lost 'em. - We lost them.
- 在哪跟丢的? - 弗农街和工业街街口
- Lost where? - vernon and lndustry.
- 他们就像人间蒸发了一样 - 在屠宰区?
- I mean they like fucking disappeared! - the slaughterhouse district?
是的 这大热天 我是说 热得能烧烤了
Yeah, and in this heat, whoo! I mean, bo and barbecue!
不管凯斯在找什么 他已找到了 或即将找到
so whatever keyes is looking for, he's found it, or damn close to it.
利昂娜 我想见金·威利
Leona, I want to meet with king willie.
看来我和威利有着相同的麻烦
Willie and I seem to have the same problem.
- 而你 跟我一起走 - 迈克 这无法办到
- In the meantime, you come with me. - Mike, it's impossible!
就这么决定了
Just do it.
该死!
Fuck!
欧米加一号 这里是控制中心
Omega 1. this is control.
这里是欧米加一号
This is omega 1.
我们只有二十二分钟安全作业时间
We only have 22 minutes on safe window of operation.
- 是 长官 - 最后一次检查遥测装置
- Yes, sir. - Verify that final telemetry check.
开始测试
Start your test now.
跟踪扫描 三 二 一
Scan track three, two, one,
开始
Mark.
六号 紫外线的正常启动
Number six, power up on the uv banks.
紫外线已经完成 准备好接受测试
We're complete on the lower uv banks. ready for testing.
第二步 检查周围的温度变化
Second level, check for ambient temperature variations.
你有两分钟时间 现在开始
You got two minutes. now get going.
所有单位
To all units.
所有单位 你们有大约20分钟时间完成任务
All units, you have approximately 20 minutes to finish your task.
- 收到 - 增加这个紫外线
- Roger. - Increase this uv.
上升到42%
Up 42 per cent.
你朋友死于利器刺入胸腔
Your friend died as the result of an intrusion in the chest cavity
这差点把他的心撕成两半
..by an edged weapon that nearly cleaved the heart in two.
死亡是瞬间发生的
Death was instantaneous.
他全身的骨头都被去掉了 我从未见过
He was boned like a fish. I've never seen anything like this.
请别碰任何东西
Please, do not touch anything.
医生 其他那些受害者的情况怎么样
Doctor, what about the other victims?
有什么别的发现吗
Anything there?
联邦调查组带来了他们自己的法医
The federal team brought in their own forensic examiners.
我是这个城市的验尸员和首席病理学家
I am the medical examiner and the chief pathologist in the city,
但是他们就这么把我完全抛弃了
and they've cut me out completely.
不管怎样 你能看到他们收集到的证据吧
Anyway you can get a look at evidence the feds have collected?
- 我是说 他们肯定做过实验 - 这很困难
- I mean, they must have run tests. - It won't be easy.
医生
Doctor,
这是我从丹尼的手里找到的
l pried this from danny's hands.
正是它把丹尼引上了屋顶
this is what took him into the rafters.
- 这个几乎没有重量 - 但它却像钢铁一样锋利
- It has almost no weight. - But it cuts like steel.
让我来看看
Let me see.
现在我们把它放大十五万倍
We are now at 150,000 times normal magnification.
真令人惊讶
Astonishing.
这种元素根本不存在于元素周期表上
This material doesn't correspond to anything on the periodic table.
- 中尉 那到底是什么 - 我不知道
- lieutenant, what the hell is that thing?  - I don't know.
但肯定不是五金店里买的
It's not from a hardware store.
- 不是军用的吗 - 很好的假设
- No military?  - Uh, good guess.
不是他们丢的 就是他们想找的
Either something that got away, or something they want.
凯斯 我们已经离真相很近了
Keyes. ah, we're getting closer now to what happened
住手
Hey, no!
放松 小伙子 把你的抢收起来
Easy, kid. put your gun away.
金·威利要见你
King willie will see you now.
- 没事 - 你不想我跟你一起去
- It's ok. - Don't you want me with you?
稍后我打给你
I'll call you later.
- 你想我跟着你吗 - 稍后我打给你
- You want me to follow you? - I'll call you later!
整点大麻怎么样
You want some ganja, man?
车牌号
License plate number.
1-8-8
1-8-8.
不不不 1- 8- 8- 3
No, no. 1-8-8-3.
该死!
Oh, fuck!
去你的"凡事都有两面"
The door swings both ways, my ass.
这事儿也有两面
This door swings both ways.
谢谢载我一程
Thanks for the ride.
你们
You know,
实在该少抽点烟
you guys really ought to cut down.
他们说你想跟我聊聊
They say you want to talk to me.
他们还说你在暗中帮助我
They say you're offering me favours.
告诉我你这么做的原因 死警察
Tell me why, babylon.
警察先生
Mr policeman.
- 我需要一些情报 - 情报?
- I want some information. - information.
关于那个杀手吗
About the one that's doing all the killing?
他先杀了你的人
He killed your people.
现在又来杀我的
Now mine.
我想你应该知道他是谁
I think you know who he is.
我想要找到他
I want him.
我不知道他是谁
I don't know who he is.
但我知道他在哪
But I know where he is.
- 在另外一个世界 - 你在胡说些什么
- The other side. - What are you talking about?
在灵界中
The spirit world, man.
看到吗
You see,
总是这样的
it's always the same.
该来的还是要来
There's no stopping what can't be stopped.
该死的还是要死
No killing what can't be killed.
别故弄玄虚了
Hey, make sense, man.
杀了你跟我的手下的那个东西
This thing that's killing your people and mine
来自另外一个世界
is from the other side.
我能感受到他的存在
I can feel him all around.
但除非他来找你
You can't see the eyes of the demon...
不然就无法用肉眼看到他
until him come calling.
这真是恐怖
This is dread, man.
非常恐怖
Truly dread.
这里没你的事了 警察先生
Nothing else for you here, policeman.
走吧
Time to go.
时刻做好准备
Prepare yourself.
"他的基地在圣山之上"
"his foundation lie in the holy mountain."
"西拉"
"selah."
这里是托尼·普波在充满恐惧的
This is tony pope live from la,
洛杉矶城为您直播
the city of fear.
那个变态的杀手还在继续着他每天的屠杀
The psycho-vigilante killer continues his daily diet for murder.
高挂的尸体
Bodies strung out,
被剥皮的尸体 以及从尸体中挖出的心脏
bodies with the skins ripped off, the hearts torn from the cadavers.
而就在刚才 金·威利 那个毒枭
And just recently, king willie, the drug lord,...
那个万恶的毒枭 在一条小巷的转角被杀了
the vicious drug lord found in an alley just around the corner...
他的头被砍了下来 而脊椎则被拆散了
with his head cut off and his spinal column torn from the body.
真是死有余辜
A fitting demise to the prince of powder.
先是丹尼 接着是金·威利 而你恰好都在
First danny, then king willie. and you were right there!
他在耍你呢 你得小心点
He's playing with you, mike. you've gotta be careful.
好的 我们都要小心 凯斯那边怎么样
Yeah. we all gotta be careful. what about keyes?
- 有新发现吗 - 凯斯这有点棘手
- Anything there? - Definitely something slippery about keyes.
全名叫彼得·J·凯斯
Seems there's a peter j keyes.
获得了是康奈尔大学的物理学博士学位
Phd physical sciences, cornell.
以优异的成绩毕业并加入战略防御研究所
Hot out of college and into the strategic defense lnstitute.
两年后被任命为空军情报部门的上尉
Then two years later commissioned as a captain in air force lntelligence.
迈克 我们查不下去了 超过我们范围了
Mike, this is a dead end. we're way out of our league!
听着 我不管他有多大的来头
Look, I don't care how big this is and who's involved.
他杀了丹尼 他必须付出代价
This guy killed danny and he's going to fall!
- 医生那边怎么样 - 我在这 中尉
- Now whatabout the good doctor? - Yeah, I'm here, lieutenant.
联邦当局清除了所有证据
The federal authorities erased everything from the computer file
除了这个
except for this
别墅的木碎片的部分化验结果
Part of a chemical test on a fragment of wood from the penthouse.
它含有微量的牛血
And it contained traces...
和大量的类固醇
..of cattle blood and heavy traces of steroids.
我认为杀死丹尼的凶手
I believe whoever killed detective
最近曾到过屠宰场
Had recently been in a slaughterhouse.
屠宰场 正是我第一次跟丢凯斯的地方
Slaughterhouse.That's where llostkeyes the first time!
恩 我们会在那找到他的
Yeah. that's where we'll find him.
坐地铁过来 一小时后伯恩斯车站见
Take the metro. I'll pick you up at Burns station in an hour.
你没看到凯斯的人 不代表他不在附近
Justbecause you don't see keyes's boys doesn't mean they're notaround.
乖乖的在车里坐着
I just want you to stay in the car. ok?
你妈妈和我马上来 坐好别乱跑
Your mom and I won't be very long. you sit still.
我们很快就回来
We'll be back in a few minutes.
明白了吗
All right?
- 走吧 亲爱的 - 恩
- Come on, honey. - Yes.
- 走哪边 - 从这边过去
- which way was it? - Down here.
受死吧 你这只癞皮狗
Take that, you scum-sucking dog.
要吃糖吗
Want some candy?
布赖恩 布赖恩
Brian? brian!
- 你立刻给我回来 - 妈咪 我看到鬼了
- You come here right this minute! - Mommy, I saw a ghost.
要吃糖吗 要吃糖吗
Wantsome candy? wantsome candy?
安息吧
Rest.
要吃糖吗
Wantsome candy?
丹尼的项链
Danny's necklace.
我讨厌在繁忙时段坐地铁
I hate the subway at rush hour.
这时段空位很难找 如果你有幸找到了
It's hard enough to find a seat, and if you do,
上面要么是有尿的 要么是有屎的
Someone's pissed in it or thrown up over it.
热死我了
This damn heat is killing me, man.
嘿 我上电视了
Hey, it's me!
- 我很上镜啊 - 臭美
- I look great! - Oh, shit.
没有签名 大叔
No autographs, pop.
- 看 那儿有两个空位 - 别碰我
- Look. there's two seats right there. - Don't touch me!
滚开
Hey! get off!
麻烦事真多
This shit never ends.
- 你来吧 - 混蛋
- After you. - Asshole!
- 请让开一下 警察办事 - 别挡路
- Excuse me. police business. - Get out of my way!
嘿 宝贝 亲我一下 来嘛
Hey, baby. besame mucho. come on!
你看上去挺有同情心的嘛
You look like a sympathetic dude.
我的兄弟最近要做点买卖
My, uh... partner here needs an operation .
但我们手头有点紧 你明白我意思吧
But we're a little short of cash, if you know what I mean?
不需要那样
No need for that.
恩 钱啊
Mm, money.
滚开
get the hell away from me!
不要逼我 我真的会开枪的
I know how to use this thing! don't make me use this thing!
我敢打赌我的枪比你的大
Bet mine's bigger than yours!
我来搞定他
I'll take that.
- 住手 警察 - 这次麻烦大了
- Hold it. police! - We're in trouble now.
- 所有人都不许动 - 警察 不许动
- Nobody move! - Alto, policia, no se muevan!
大家深呼吸 别紧张
Everybody take a deep breath, loosen your sphincters.
别逞一时之勇
We don't need any rush-hour rambos there.
把枪放下 混球
Tu tambien, motherfucking baby!
放下枪 然后坐下 坐下
Drop it and sit down! sientate!
妈的那是什么
What the hell is that?
利昂娜 你还好吧
leona, you ok?
它在车厢里 带乘客们离开
This is it! he's in the train! get these people out of here!
吉瑞
Jerry!
发生什么事
What's happening?
趴下 趴下
Get down! get down!
快离开
Get out of the way!
吉瑞
Jerry!
利昂娜
Leona!
利昂娜 带他们走 走啊
Leona, get 'em out! go! go!
快
Now!
吉瑞
Jerry!
利昂娜 快走啊
Leona, do it!
快
Now!
我在这里
Hey! over here!
对了 过来吧
Yeah, that's right. come and get it.
快点 走啊 走啊
Come on! move it! move it!
走快点 走
Let's go! vamos!
走
move it!
别慌 走就可以了 走 快走
Don't panic, just go! go! vamos!
天哪 你是什么东西啊
Jesus christ. what the fuck are you?
等一下
Wait!
走啊 走啊 快点
Vamos!vamos! come on!
向前走啊 快 你们两个 走啊
Keep walking! come on, you too! vamonos!
来啊 狗娘养的
Come on, motherfucker!
要吃糖吗
Wantsome candy?
让我们跳舞吧
Let's dance!
快让开
Come on, get out of the way!
让开
Get out of the way!
快 出来 出来
Come on, out! out! out!
快点 跑
Come on, move it!
去那边 去有光的地方
That way! that way! towards the light! the light!
快 都出来
Come on! get out!
快点啊
Come on.
走
Vamos!
天哪
Oh, god.
吉瑞
Jerry.
上帝 怎么又杀人了
God, not again.
快离开 别挡着
Ok, move your ass! move out the way!
发生了什么事
Watch out! what's happening?
他妈的真是一场屠杀 中尉
It's a fucking slaughter, lieutenant.
天啊
Oh, god!
吉瑞
Hey, jerry!
利昂娜
Oh, leona! leona!
醒醒 利昂娜
Oh, please. leona... oh.
- 她怎样了 - 还活着 但过度惊吓
- how's she doing? - deep shock, but she's alive.
我听到胎儿的心跳 她怀孕了
I hear foetal heart sounds. she's pregnant.
立刻送到洛杉矶医治
Let's move. la county. stat!
让开点
Stand back.
数三下 一 二 三 起
On three. one, two, three. load up.
让开
Out of my way!
让开 快走开
Move out the way! move it! move it!
等一下 让我看看
Uh, wait a minute. let me see.
- 吉瑞在哪 - 我不知道
- Where's jerry? - I don't know.
我们找到了他的警章
We found his badge.
哪些人受伤了
Who got hit this time?
五个小混混
Five gang members,...
一些乘客
..bunch of commuters.
这说不通啊
Doesn't make sense.
他们都有带枪
They were all armed.
- 什么意思 - 指挥官的电话
- What do you mean? - It's the chief.
在这等着 喂
Wait here. yeah?
- 那边情况怎么了 - 他妈的很糟
- What the hell's going on down there? - It's a damn nightmare.
这次遇害的都是平民
Civilians this time.
- 全都死了吗 - 是 和之前的一样
- Allkilled? - Yeah. just like the others.
妈的
Damn!
吉瑞
Jerry!
活见鬼 他妈的发生了什么事
Holy shit! what the hell is going on here?
伙计 打开摄像机 快开摄像机
Hey, guys, get the camera on! get the camera on this right now!
拍下这些事
Get that goddamn thing on film!
发生了什么事
What's going on?
哈里根
Hey, harrigan!
这次受害人更多 损毁更严重
More victims! more mutilations!
- 去死吧 - 普波
- Fuck you! - Pope!
普波 你还在吗 普波 发生了什么事
Pope? are you there, pope? pope, what's going on?
长官 那个警察又来了
Sir, the cop is back.
妈的
Goddamn.
哈里根 你就不能省点儿力气吗
Harrigan! don't you show up in the damnedest places.
过来 中尉 我有些你会感兴趣的东西
Come here, lieutenant. I got something you might find interesting.
这里是怎么回事
What is this?
我要跟你说多少遍
How many times do I have to tell you?
你不知道你的对手是什么
You don't know what you're dealing with.
这个就是你要找的凶手 很妙吧
There's your killer. wonderful, isn't it?
他的身躯散发出信息素 即气味分子
Pheromone signature left by his body. scent molecules.
打开三号监视器
Punch up three.
十年前 一只同种类的异形在中美洲
Ten years ago one of his kind eliminated an
摧毁了一支特种精英部队
Elite special forces crew in central america.
只有两个幸存者
There were two survivors.
他们说 这种生物一旦被捕
They indicated that, when trapped,
就会启动一种自毁程式
The creature activated a self-destruct device...
威力足以摧毁三百个街区那么大的雨林
..that destroyed enough rainforest to cover 300 city blocks.
完美的武器
Remarkable weaponry.
没错 中尉 他是外星生物
That's right, lieutenant. other-world life forms.
什么
Huh?
一只他妈的异形
A fucking alien!
硫磺岛 柬埔寨 贝鲁特
Iwo jima, cambodia, beirut.
发出热能和引起矛盾
Drawn by heat and conflict.
他在进行着狩猎游戏 狮子 老虎 熊
He's on safari. lions. the tigers. the bears.
我的天
Oh, my!
奖品 那是一场游戏 对吧 凯斯
Trophies. that's the game, isn't it, keyes?
你就是狮子
You're the lion.
这里是它的丛林
This is his jungle.
那为什么我们看不到它
So why can't we see him?
因为它有超强的自卫适应系统
defensive adaptations are astounding.
它能弯曲光线 完美的伪装术
It's somehow able to bend light. perfect camouflage.
- 你欣赏这只怪物 - 不是它的所作所为
- you admire the son of a bitch. - not what he does.
而是它本身的构造
For what he is.
还有它能带给我们的东西
For what he can give us.
这将会是科技的一个新时代
A new era of scientific technology.
我一生都在等这机会 我不会让它白白溜走
I've waited a lifetime for this, and I'm not going to miss the chance.
信息素雷达扫描仪发现它了
We have something on the pheromone scanners.
目标在屋顶上
Target one is on the roof.
我们花了两周的时间摸清了它的习惯
it's taken us two weeks to learn his patterns.
它每隔两天就来这里开餐一次
He comes here every two days to feed.
- 看来它很喜欢牛肉 - 我没觉得是素食者
- seems he has a taste for beef. - I didn't think he was vegetarian.
我们为这只食肉兽准备了一个陷阱
Well, we've prepared a trap for this predator.
我们肯定这种生物
We are certain that this being can see in
只能用红外线看物体
only one spectrum of light infrared.
红外线?
Infrared?
它靠感应热量捕食
He hunts by seeing our heat.
隔绝了热量 它就是瞎子
Block the heat and he's blind.
这衣服能隔绝身体的热量 使它看不到我们
These suits insulate body heat, making the team invisible to the creature.
我们在地面上覆盖了一层放射性粉末
We've flooded the place with radioactive dust...
并在每一个角落都安装上强紫外光灯
..and installed powerful ultraviolet lighting everywhere.
这种粉末粘附在它身上就会使它现形
The dust adheres to his body, making him visible.
液氮 你们不是要杀它而是要冰冻它
Liquid nitrogen. you're not gonna kill him. you're gonna freeze him.
- 我们要生擒它 - 它在移动了
- We have to capture him. - He's moving.
终于来了
Finally.
找个位子 好好看表演吧
Grab a seat. enjoy the show.
这是历史性的时刻
This is history.
我们的目标是生擒并隔离它
Capture and isolation is our objective.
只有在我下令的时候才能防卫
Defensive action only on my orders.
开灯 行动
Power up. lights on. let's get him!
我们已经进入
We're in.
切换到紫外线
Switch to ultraviolet.
-  停止通话 - 打开A到J区的紫外线灯
- Radio silence. out. - engage ultraviolet units a through j.
- 这些干扰信号是什么 - 正在调整 长官
- What's all this interference? - Correcting the problem, sir.
他们正在走向二区
They're moving to the second level.
目标仍在朝二号楼梯井移动
Target's still moving, heading towards the number two stairwell.
它正在往陷阱里钻
Playing right into it.
等一下
Wait a minute.
它停住了
It's stopped.
它退到墙边了
It's moving back against the wall.
它正往回走 离他们越来越远了
It's backing up. it's moving away from them.
你的人被耍了
Your boys have been made.
长官 它现在在他们周围兜圈
Sir, it's circling around behind them.
让他们出来 他们掉进陷阱里了
Get 'em out! they're walking into a trap!
凯斯 它在三楼 就在你们后面
Keyes, he's behind you. third floor structure. right there!
谁在那里啰嗦 不准通讯
Who is this? clear the line.
它看得见那该死的光 把他们关掉 关掉
He sees the damn lights. turn 'em off! turn 'em off! shit!
制止他
Stop him!
- 把门打开 - 你去死吧
- Door. open it. - Go fuck yourself.
好啊 好
Ok. ok.
开门
The door.
- 好的 我开 - 你知道你在做什么吗
- Yes, sir. - You don't know what you're doing.
开了
It's open.
- 你会把所有东西搞砸的 - 去死吧
- You'll ruin everything!  - Fuck yourself!
防卫队形一 液氮枪关闭
Defensive formation one. nitrogen guns, safeties off.
大家跟着我
Everyone else, follow me .
它就在这里
This is it.
它正向你们移动 右边
He's moving down to your position, right.
盖博 它在哪儿 我看不到它
Garber, where is he? I can't see him.
它就在那里 它就在那里
He's right there! he's right there!
妈的 它在哪儿 告诉我它的坐标
Goddamn it! where is he? well, give me a coordinate! where is he?
- 小心 - 天哪
- Watch out! - My god.
小心你的枪
Watch your crossfire!
妈的
Damn!
我的防护衣漏气了
I'm losing my pressure.
凯斯 你怎样了
Keyes, you all right?
凯斯 它在这里
Keyes, it's overhere!
快 妈的
Come on! damn it.push over!
妈的 我什么都看不到
Shit! I can't see!
通讯都中断了
They're gone.
他们全死了
They're all dead.
你想杀我吗 我就在这儿
You want me? here lam!
你真是一只
You are one...
丑陋的
..ugly mother...
混蛋
Motherfucker!
猜猜谁回来啦
Guess who's back.
你回不了家啦
Too late to go home now.
快离开这里 哈里根 我来救你
Get out of here, harrigan. I'm gonna save your ass.
这是我和他之间的战斗
This is between me and him!
天哪...
God...
原来是鸟
Birds.
该死的鸟
Damn birds.
好吧 脓包脸
Ok, pussyface
动手吧
It's your move.
好戏上演
Shit happens.
啊 天哪
Oh, god. oh, god.
我现在需要像鸟一样
That's all I need is birds.
你行的
You can do it.
我可以做到的 我行的
I can do it. I can do it.
就像从树上滑下来那样
It's like falling off a log.
妈的 三十层楼高的树
Like a 30-storey log. damn!
我可能会很好运地到达
Maybe I'll get lucky and fall.
妈的
Damn it.
伯伦加利亚 在赛普洛斯嫁给国王以后
..berengaria, who never set foot in england, was its queen for eightyears...
当了八十年的皇后 却从未踏足英国
..aftermarrying this king on cyprus.
晚安
goodluck.
赫伯 赫伯 醒醒
Herb? Herb, wake up!
有人在我们家浴室
There's somebody in the bathroom.
赫伯
Herb!
- 别怕 我是警察 - 我不认为它怕你
- It's all right. I'm a cop. - I don't think he gives a shit.
妈的
Shit!
快回屋里去
Get back inside!
妈的 又要往下滑
Holy moses. not again. shit!
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
上帝啊
Oh, god.
为什么这只怪物不呆在地面上啊
Why can't this guy stay on the ground?
过来 过来
Come on, come on. come on, come on!
过来这里
Come to papa.
停 把电梯停住
Stop! stop the elevator!
停啊
Stop it!
这是什么鬼地方啊
Now where the hell am l?
你在哪
Where are you?
上帝啊
Jesus christ.
这就对了 混蛋
That's right, asshole!
好戏上演
Shit happens!
好 谁接着来
Ok. who's next?
拿去
Take... it.
1715年
"1715."
哈里根 那里他妈的发生了什么事
Harrigan! what the fuck happened in there, huh?
活见鬼 我们差点就成功了
Goddamn it. we came so close!
别担心 混球 你还会有机会的
Don't worry, asshole. you'll get another chance.